{
    "id": "f3ce69c704f7461882e113be15a72f84",
    "title": "Modals Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "…………………….. you mind moving a bit?",
            "description": "Would is used in polite requests.",
            "answers": [
                "Will",
                "Would",
                "Should"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………… you lend me your vacuum cleaner?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Will",
                "Shall",
                "Should"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "You ……………………….. not repeat this.",
            "description": "Shall can express an order when used with second and third person pronouns.",
            "answers": [
                "shall",
                "may",
                "might"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "You ……………………….. pay for this.",
            "description": "When used with second and third person pronouns, shall can indicate a threat.",
            "answers": [
                "shall",
                "should",
                "would"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………… I call the doctor?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Should",
                "Would",
                "Will"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "All students ………………………… submit their assignments by Friday.",
            "description": "Should indicates obligation. ",
            "answers": [
                "would",
                "should",
                "could"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "You …………………………… leave early if you are not feeling well.",
            "description": "Either can or may is possible here. ",
            "answers": [
                "can",
                "may",
                "will"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "You ………………………….. not have done this to me.",
            "description": "The expression should not have is used to criticize people for doing things.",
            "answers": [
                "would",
                "should",
                "will"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The workers asked if they ………………………… leave early.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "would",
                "can",
                "could"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………………… sing better when I was younger.",
            "description": "We use could to indicate past ability.",
            "answers": [
                "should",
                "would",
                "could"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "If I knew his name, I ………………………. tell you.",
            "description": "In the second conditional we use a simple past in the if-clause and would + first form of the verb in the main clause.",
            "answers": [
                "will",
                "would",
                "should"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He hung up before I ............................. say a word.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "can",
                "could",
                "would"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}